Hello!
Hi, servus!
I'm at Dino's Dino-Armstand.
What do I find here?
You find belts in different colors.
I thought the fetish scene needs not only a little latex color, but also in the leather area.
And then I thought in 2019, man, make a little color, bring a little color into the game.
And these are not just belts, I think I've seen neckbands too?
Shoulder straps, the right foot and arm straps,
Lines, doggy handles and the pigtails are also in the same color.
And you can also take the luggage itself, the handbag or the weekender,
and make it out of the same leather as the product that you use later for playing.
I also have a dress from the Belgian fashion.
What would you wear on it to make it a bit colorful?
Because the stones in the silver look are shiny and round, we take the first piece that hangs there.
In silver we pack the hinge in, which you can vary in different holes, so that it is always centered in the back.
So that it is always centered in the back, because it is centered in the front and right and left.
I'll put it on top of you.
So, this is the belt, the O-belt in metallic silver.
And you can also put the O-belt on by holding on to the straps or the doggy handles that come right and left.
As I said, you can pull it through the loops from the back and then give more pressure from the back to the opposite side.
For example, the leash. The belt is not only for sub-women, but also for the dom woman.
You can hang the leash here.
You can also hang your SAP.
It's already chic.
It's super chic, look at that.
I'll give you a moment.
Feel it.
You can take off the leash and put the SAP on the neckband.
But you don't have to hold the leash.
You can just let it run next to you.
Or just as an accessory.
On the other hand, the sap can also be felt on the belt, by having the linen on the belt instead of the neckband.
Then the breathing is sometimes more pleasant.
Yes, that's what we have here.
And the arm or foot straps fit.
And here we have different options, that you can do it directly here with the carabiner part and fix it.
Or just fix it in the back, fix it in the front, crosswise.
Quite practical. Super practical.
This is two times lime leather or rinsed leather and riveted and still sewn.
And on top of that, the eyelets are from the boat construction, stainless steel eyelets, welded and they really hold up.
Yes, and then the dress is a little more open. A little more colorful.
Yes. I have the right waistband for the belt. Do I have to put it down? No.
No.
The fields. That's quite practical to keep it with this thing here, yes? Yes.
Okay. A cow that wants to be a leopard. Yes.
Here we have the V-form.
Can you play?
Yes.
Pussy.
Pussy, right?
Compared to the other one.
You always think the big ones are too gloomy or something.
Yes, they look like from the box.
But in the end they make a nicer part from the form.
Like the V-form at the end of the day.
At the end of the day.
The round ones don't cut that much, of course.
There's more mass there.
That's it for now.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
I thank you.
Bye.
The tree is really nice.
Yes, the tree with everything.
The tree with a lot.
Wait a minute, then I'll put my thing back in here.
The cylinder comes in.
Yes.
Woah, stop it!